- [Ruru] Okay, let's head back.
- [Ma-kun] Sounds good. See ya.
[Ruru] Bye-bye.
- I'm back!
- Come on in.
- No sauna magic, I'm afraid.
- What?
- [Assun] Why not?
- [Ruru] Well, you know…
RURU (26)
MODEL
I said, "If you wanted to eat yakiniku,
but your girlfriend wanted to eat sushi,
then what would you do?"
And he was like, "Well, if I want
yakiniku, then that's what we're eating."
- He was like, "No compromise."
- Oh, God.
- [Hikaru] I see how it is.
- [Assun] That's a red flag.
[Ruru] That's what I was thinking.
How's he so different when we try
to have deep conversations one-on-one?
You get a totally different impression
one-on-one.
That's wild.
He's more immature than I thought.
Exactly! I don't know, for some reason,
I expected him to be way more mature.
Yeah, honestly, I don't know.
ASSUN (30)
ENTREPRENEUR AND HOSTESS
- [Maririn] Hard pass.
- [Ruru] I'm disappointed.
He's just a pretty face.
That's all he has.
Didn't the letter thing
make your heart pound?
[Tai-chan] It was nerve-wracking.
Whose did you put yours in?
- Whose mailbox?
- [Tai-chan] Mmm.
- Tai-chan thinks she gave him her letter.
- Right.
Interesting.
Honestly…
Mmm… Ma-kun. [giggles]
Wait, then who put one in mine?
Well, you know who now.
So it's her? Maririn.
- Okay, I get it.
- That's it.
I just assumed that
the letter was from you.
Oh, did you really?
Do the girls hate me?
Did I make a bad impression?
- Not at all.
- Really?
Yeah, it's still the first day.
Or, it's been 24 hours.
I mean, still, by now it's pretty clear
I have strong feelings for you, right?
I'd say so.
So you're down to two choices now.
[Tai-chan] I'm quick with everything.
I like to go fast.
- Even saying how I feel.
- [Hikaru] Mmm.
That can be both, good and bad.
I'm a speedster, what can I say?
- You're a speedster? [chuckles]
- [Tai-chan] Big time. No doubt.
Look, I mean, Ruru is a model, so yeah,
part of me was attracted to her.
But right now,
I'm getting close to Hikaru,
or it's more like my feelings for her are…
speeding way up.
[opening theme song playing]
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RAPPER FROM SAGAMIHARA
SPITTING LYRICS OF PURE LOVE
ARI
KAWASAKI'S IT-GIRL HOSTESS
OUT TO FIND A REAL MAN
HIKARU
KYOTO BAR OWNER
GOING ALL-IN FOR HIS WOMAN
NANIWA'S BARROOM BEAUTY
LOOKING FOR TRUE LOVE
MARIRIN
KURUME YANKII
WHO GREW UP BEHIND BARS
BO
EX-YAKUZA MMA FIGHTER
LOOKING FOR HIS RIDE-OR-DIE
MA-KUN
NAGOYA'S NO.1 HOSTESS
WHO PUTS MEN IN THEIR PLACE
ASSUN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST
WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
AN HONEST MODEL
IN SEARCH OF LOVE
RURU
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
Right, let's eat!
- [Maririn] Dig in.
- [Tai-chan] Let's eat!
Looks delicious.
- What is this again?
- Carbonara?
- Wait, are you sure?
- Oh, is that wrong?
Why don't we dive deeper
into Maririn's story today?
- [Ruru] Totally.
- [Assun] You want to?
- [Ruru] I want to hear more from her.
- Can I have a drink first?
- [Assun] It's tough to do it sober.
- Don't know if "tough" is the word, but…
Let's give her the floor.
- [Ari] I want to hear.
- [Assun] Go ahead.
[Ma-kun] You should talk too.
Anything to share, Maririn?
But you don't have to force yourself.
It's only been two days.
[Assun] True.
Just whenever you feel like talking.
Probably be easier
if she had booze in her.
[Ma-kun] Wanna wait till we're drinking?
- It's okay, it doesn't have to be today.
- [Assun] Yeah.
- Huh?
- [Nagano] Wait, what's wrong?
What's going on?
- [Bo] What's wrong?
- [sniffles]
- Some stuff is coming up.
- [Leo] Hey, it's okay.
MA-KUN (28)
MMA FIGHTER
You okay, Maririn? What's up?
- [Maririn sobbing]
- [Ruru] You don't have to talk about it.
- [Leo] Don't push yourself.
- [Ruru] Exactly.
Yeah. Oh, hey, you shouldn't open
a letter with "Wassup."
ARI (29)
RAPPER & MODEL
- [Leo] Seriously.
- [Ma-kun] That's crazy, man. No way.
[Assun] We laughed so hard
when we saw that.
- [Ari] Who'd do that?
- He did.
- [Ari] Come on.
- Go smoke?
- I wanna go with you, Hikaru.
- [Hikaru] Wanna go?
- [Ruru] Huh?
- Should we go?
You want to? [sniffles]
BRING ON LIFE
Classrooms?
Whoa, this is crazy. [chuckles]
[Tai-chan] Takes you back, doesn't it?
[Maririn chuckles]
Let's gaze into
each other's eyes and talk.
- Gaze into your eyes?
- Yeah.
- [sighs]
- [Tai-chan] Why were you crying earlier?
- Don't have to say if you don't want to.
- Mmm. [sniffles]
Well, uh, honestly, like,
I don't even know where to start.
- [Tai-chan] Yeah.
- [sniffles]
But, like, all my boyfriends were abusive,
and the worst guy I was with was…
He was basically a thug.
Like, just a bad guy in general.
This one time
he grabbed my head and… [sniffles]
…he kept saying he was going to,
like, cut me open,
and make me bleed out
and rip off my nails in the bathroom.
[sniffles] And he was serious,
told me to go in there.
I know he'd actually killed someone too,
and he pointed a gun at me
and stuff, so… [exhales]
I don't know,
he basically took everything I had.
He destroyed my whole life.
Huh?
[sniffles] So, yeah.
I just… [sobs]
I've never been loved by anyone, and…
[sobbing, sniffling]
And I don't know why
I've had to go through this much pain.
I don't even know who he was,
he lied about his name and everything.
So, yeah.
I mean,
that's a pretty heavy story, right?
I feel like…
that heaviness is coming out here
and I seem really gloomy to everyone.
I don't know how to have
a real relationship.
A lot of times I go along
with whatever the other person says
'cause I'm afraid I'm gonna get hit.
So, I always end up kind of
fading into the background.
And it gets harder and harder
to express myself.
[sniffles]
- Sorry.
- Dang, that's… Yeah.
[Maririn chuckles, sniffles] Yeah.
Sorry. Thanks. [laughs, sniffles]
You can't just share that, I get it.
Not in a group.
But the thing is, like…
I do really want to be loved by someone
'cause I don't know
what real love is like.
I thought if I came here…
someone might finally
express real feelings for me.
Thanks for listening
while looking me in the eye.
No problem.
And, yeah, I…
I guess I do feel better getting it out
'cause I don't really
tell people about this.
[Tai-chan] Oh, right.
- [Maririn] This isn't too heavy?
- No way.
- [Maririn] You really mean that?
- Yeah.
[Maririn] Anyway, um, thanks. [sniffles]
I hope that we can both experience…
- [Maririn] Mmm.
- …real love here.
[Nagano] Tai-chan's a good guy.
I'm glad you invited me.
- [Tai-chan] Yeah?
- Thanks for inviting me.
- [Tai-chan] Don't mention it.
- [chuckles]
[Megumi] It turns out that Maririn
- has some serious scars.
- [Nagano] Right?
- [Ari] Let's take a picture.
- [Hikaru] A Polaroid! Let's do it!
- On three, "Wassup, man,"
- [both] One, two, three.
- Wassup, man!
- [giggles]
Amazing. [laughs]
- Not bad at all.
- What was that?
We nailed this one.
I think it's the first time
- I've taken a Polaroid with a girl.
- Me too.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
I feel like the two of us,
out of everyone here,
people see us as the jokers,
the loudmouths,
but it's interesting to see what it's like
when it's just the two of us.
- Mmm. They see us like the class clowns.
- Very much so. [laughs]
- Like, we don't know what's going on?
- Totally.
No, exactly.
But I think we're serious when it matters.
- Like when it comes to love.
- Mmm.
I'm definitely misunderstood.
Especially 'cause I work at a hostess bar,
so people assume I'm a total slut.
But I'm really innocent.
Hey, boss,
are we allowed to say "slut" here?
- [chuckles]
- We've decided to let it slide this once.
Oh, very nice.
- You're from Kanagawa?
- Mmm.
Me too.
Kawasaki is close to where you are?
- Yeah.
- We're close enough
- that rumors about me could reach you.
- [Ari] I gotcha.
But, whatever you hear about me,
there's no way it'll be that I'm a slut.
No chance.
- [Ari] 'Cause you're the opposite?
- Yup.
Oh, okay, gotcha.
Damn, that hit me kinda hard just now.
You saying,
"You'll never hear that about me".
I've never heard that before.
- That's really rare.
- I'm legit innocent.
Good to know.
Wait, so is there someone
you're interested in right now?
Like, are you vibing with anyone?
Honestly, I hope not.
I hope it's just me, you know?
- Why are you smirking? [chuckles]
- [Hikaru giggles]
You have my letter
in your pocket, don't you?
- Yeah. Why do you ask?
- Why? Because I actually--
I have super sloppy handwriting,
and I half-assed it because I was wasted.
- Thanks for this.
- [laughing] No, stop it.
- [Tai-chan] Want me to stop?
- No, you can keep looking at it. [laughs]
Um… [sniffles]
No, I wanna write it again,
but better this time.
- [chuckles]
- [Nagano exclaims]
- [Megumi] She's here.
- Excuse me. Sorry, guys.
- Can I crash your party for a second?
- [Maririn] Crash away.
- [Tai-chan] Sure.
- [Maririn] Yeah.
- There goes the "Let you have him."
- "Can I crash your party?"
- She's something, isn't she?
- [Megumi] How can she just
- barge into a conversation like that?
- [Nagano] I don't know.
What should I do?
Are the three of us
going to talk together? Or…
- Either way is…
- Okay if we chat alone for a second?
- [Maririn] For sure.
- [Hikaru] Cool?
[Maririn] You gonna go smoke?
- Do you mind?
- Go ahead.
- Right, then. Sorry, okay?
- [Maririn] No worries. [chuckles softly]
[Tai-chan] Okay…
I mean…
- The girls are assertive.
- Finally, moves are being made!
- Definitely some palpable tension there.
- Here we go!
- Real quick. Hmm?
- [Tai-chan] So you came back to me, huh?
- I thought you would.
- [Hikaru] Why?
[Tai-chan] You came back.
- What do you mean by, "You came back"?
- Glad you did.
But, then again, you're the guy.
- Mmm.
- Know what I mean?
- Huh?
- You're the guy.
- What do you mean?
- You're the guy, right?
- I am a guy.
- I mean…
[Tai-chan] I should've come to get you?
- [Hikaru scoffs] Obviously.
- [Tai-chan] Right, sorry.
- It's not like that. Hear me out.
- Remember what you said earlier?
[Tai-chan] Hmm? Yeah.
- Earlier?
- Hmm.
- That you were torn between two people.
- Oh, yeah.
- I feel like you're not torn, though.
- No, listen.
Earlier, when we were all talking,
she was crying, right?
- It took me off guard.
- Mmm-hmm.
Not about that. That's not what I mean.
The reason why I came
to get you just now is,
earlier today, you kind of…
made it seem like you were torn
between two people,
so I was like, "Wait, what the…"
Mmm.
- When the timing…
- [Hikaru] Mmm.
…was right for me to leave,
I was gonna go see…
- I told you that, didn't I?
- Mmm-hmm.
So, yeah, the plan was to come to you.
- Really?
- [Tai-chan] Yeah.
- I wanted to.
- Okay, yeah.
- Sorry about that.
- I kinda want you to be forward.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, if that's how you really feel.
If you mean it
when you say you're interested in me,
you can be more assertive.
The fact that I'm the youngest,
for some reason,
- is really holding me back inside--
- Age is nothing but a number.
- Agree. Age gaps don't mean anything.
- [Hikaru] It doesn't matter, at all.
Yeah, I can be more forward.
I mean, sometimes age matters,
- but out in society.
- I wanna talk one-on-one.
Let's do it. Cool. Invite me.
For sure, I will.
'Cause I think you're super cute.
- That makes me happy.
- Yeah?
- Keep telling me I'm cute, okay?
- [Tai-chan] I can do that.
I'll make sure
I start first thing in the morning.
- Sneak over to your bed.
- [chuckles]
- [Tai-chan] I'll say it all the time.
- [Hikaru] But act like you mean it too.
[Tai-chan] If I didn't plan to,
it wouldn't make sense to be here.
[Hikaru] That's right.
[Tai-chan] And if I do something
out of pocket, just smack me.
- Don't hold back.
- [Hikaru] Okay.
[Tai-chan]
Slap me and say, "You're all talk!"
- Maririn!
- She's writing another letter all alone?
- Heartbreaking. [groans]
- [Megumi exclaims]
I wanna get to know you better.
I want us both
to get to know each other, so…
- [Tai-chan] Wanna be real with me?
- Yeah.
[Tai-chan] I want that too. A lot.
- I can't stand fake people.
- Can I interrupt?
- Yeah.
- For sure.
- I actually rewrote my letter.
- Oh.
- You can read it in your room later.
- [Tai-chan] Will do.
- Thanks.
- Thanks. Sorry about that.
What does she mean, rewrote her letter?
- [Tai-chan] Hey, keep it down.
- What did she mean?
- [Tai-chan] The letter from yesterday?
- Yeah.
[Tai-chan]
It was based on first impressions…
[mellow music playing]
[Maririn] Well, basically,
I wrote that I was interested in him. And…
Also, like, um,
when he left the room with Hikaru,
he said something like, "I'm sorry, okay?"
So I put in the letter that
I got a little jealous in that moment.
I just hope it gives him
a sense of how I feel. That's all.
He's been carrying my letter around.
I just thought that was really cute.
I didn't think she'd go out of her way
like that to rewrite the letter.
But the thing is,
I can't help that Hikaru is kind of
always on my mind, so it's kind of… Yeah.
So, how was the sauna?
Well, I think for me, it made me realize
I might be more interested in you, Leo.
More than Mao… or, Ma-kun.
- What?
- [Megumi] Oh, my, my, my, my.
- After going to the sauna today?
- Yeah.
- Why's that?
- I didn't really…
feel the sauna magic
with Ma-kun, you know?
Oh…
Like, I kept genuinely thinking,
"Oh, I'd rather be talking
to Leo right now instead of Ma-kun."
Mmm. That makes me happy too.
I was really moved by your letter.
I mean it.
[Ruru] Oh, seriously?
For real.
- It hit me hard.
- Mmm.
Like, I'm already, uh…
When I first showed up here,
with everyone,
- I was in full-on bad boy mode.
- Mmm.
That's fading
and love is taking its place.
Wow.
- Super happy to hear that.
- [Leo] I mean that.
Your letter took my breath away,
I told everyone that.
- That's so cool.
- [Leo] Yeah.
But the moment you went to the sauna,
I was back in fight mode.
[laughs]
With Leo, I kind of…
I didn't get butterflies,
and I don't really know why.
[exclaiming]
- What is wrong with her?
- Yeah, I wonder what her deal is.
I just didn't feel a romantic spark.
So, yeah.
It's kind of a mystery, even to me.
I couldn't tell you why
there wasn't a stronger connection there.
But I wanna keep getting to know him.
I kind of want him to do something
about his fashion choices.
Come on, Leo's outfit today was so lame.
His style just makes him
look like a party animal,
those tight-fitting jeans
that have a cheap looking-wash.
The whole time, I was thinking,
"No bad boy would be caught dead
in those pants in the 21st century."
In the end, it's about personality,
but fashion sense is really important too.
For both, men and women.
[bell chiming]
- [Ari] Morning.
- [Leo] Hey, guys.
- [Maririn] Morning.
- [Ma-kun] Morning.
- [Leo] Here we go.
- [boy on PA] Time for Ethics class.
Life begins when you stop running
from your past, and embrace who you are.
Please reflect on the mistakes
you've made in your life,
and discuss them amongst yourselves.
Listen with compassion
to the regrets of others,
and try to learn from them.
Think about your own mistakes.
[Ari] They do this discussion thing
in other countries, right?
[boy on PA] First up is Bo.
- [Ari] You're up.
- [Boy on PA] Go ahead.
- [Ari] Get up there, Bo.
- [Ruru chuckling]
- Take it away.
- [Ari] Wassup?
- Thank you.
- [Ruru] He's the teacher.
[Bo] Um, let's see…
After I graduated from elementary school,
most of the people around me
were doing really bad stuff.
So I just naturally
fell in with them. [sniffles]
I was about 17 when I got back
from juvenile training school
the second time.
So, after I came back that time,
things were smooth for a while,
and then, when I was 21 or so,
I tried drugs for the first time.
And I struggled a lot.
Who introduced you to meth?
[inhales] It was pretty much friends
and older classmates.
Good job staying clean.
Well, now… Now, it's not that.
Like, after I got out,
I thought about using constantly.
But with the support and love
of people around me,
I was able to move forward in life.
It helps a lot to be here too.
The environment you're in matters,
that's definitely another thing I…
realized.
- Were you shooting up?
- [laughing]
- Or were you smoking?
- Bo.
- You smoked? Which one?
- They're curious.
- I smoked it.
- [Assun] You weren't injecting it.
If I injected,
I probably wouldn't have recovered.
[Maririn] That's true.
There's a difference.
- Just came out and asked?
- Yeah.
You'd be fine if you smoked it.
- [Nagano] Oh, is that so?
- Yeah, just don't inject.
- Some of the stuff Awich says is shocking.
- Yeah, she makes me a little nervous.
There's a big difference.
- You know a lot about this. "Needle?"
- Mmm, that's true.
- Suspicious.
- I'd get it if it was us, but the ladies?
- [Ari] Yeah, the girls.
- [Ma-kun] "Smoking, shooting up"? Chill.
- [Leo laughs]
- But you can't get arrested.
- [Leo] Yeah.
- [Bo] I know.
For all of our sake's, actually.
- [Ruru] Yeah.
- You're right.
- Like, we eat all of our meals together…
- [Ma-kun] Mmm.
- Don't know if I'd say we're family yet--
- We are family. What's wrong with you?
[all laughing]
- [Ruru] What a man.
- Thanks for saying that.
I think all of us probably want you
to take care of yourself
and find happiness in your life.
- [Bo] Hmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
Thanks, guys. [chuckles]
[boy on PA] Thank you.
Maririn, it's your turn. Please stand up.
Okay.
- [laughing]
- [Assun] Ms. Maririn.
- [Ari] Say good morning.
- [Ruru] Take it away.
So the reason my life
went off the rails was…
Well, let's see…
The biggest reason was that
I didn't live with my parents.
I was always a grandma's girl, I guess.
My grandma raised me, so…
The thing is,
I never wanted to be a burden to her.
So, during my first year of middle school,
I started working at night.
Mostly at girls bars.
I kind of hardly went to school.
And I lived in a rented room.
And then… [sighs]
Oh, another reason
why I didn't want to be at home was…
Well, my grandpa would, um, take his cane,
and be like, "Go back to your country."
I'd never even lived there before.
He'd say that over and over
and hit me with his cane.
What?
So, yeah, because of stuff like that,
I didn't want to be at home,
and I did things
I can't tell people about.
- That's about it.
- [Ruru] Mmm.
- [Maririn] I guess that's how it started.
So basically, your own family
was really racist toward you?
Yeah. My grandpa was from an older
generation, so I kind of get it. Still…
That was tough
for a girl in middle school.
- [Ruru] I bet.
- [Nagano] Oh, my God, what a story.
- [Ari] I can relate to that.
- [Maririn] Mmm.
Even though I'm from Kanagawa,
people would say to me, like,
"Get out of my country" and stuff.
- I was always thinking, "I was born here."
- [Maririn] That's right. Right.
[Ruru] Did your grandma protect you
when your grandpa said that stuff?
She did try to protect me at first, but,
then grandpa started
using his cane on her, and that was that.
- [Assun] Oh…
- So I was like,
"I can't do this.
I'm gonna live on my own."
- [Assun] Mmm.
- [Maririn] It was hard.
Around that time I started thinking,
"Is anyone ever gonna love me?"
All of my boyfriends were abusive.
- [Assun] What?
- [Maririn] That's how it was.
Yeah, so I'm always carrying
- this need to be loved.
- [Assun] Makes sense you'd want affection.
I'm craving it 'cause I don't know
what real love is, or…
My family never showed it to me.
The way families in TV shows hold hands,
hug, play with each other's hair,
I didn't think any of that was real.
That was when I started to think,
"Oh, I'm not normal."
[Assun] But maybe coming here
is an opportunity to change.
Yeah, totally, I think it could be.
You don't get a chance to talk about
your problems like this in the real world.
Mmm.
That's right, and it doesn't
have to be romantic love.
I just want you to experience
genuine connection here.
- Even just the bond between friends.
- The love of a friend can change you.
Just hearing your story really makes me
want to show you that.
- [Assun] Yeah.
- Thanks, guys.
[mellow music playing]
Yeah, I do think friends are important.
- Really important.
- They are.
Right, just someone you can rely on.
I get how hard it is to be in a place
where you don't have that. [sniffles]
And I know not having
any love in your life
probably seems like the norm for you,
but a lot of us here, most of us,
hopefully, we know…
[Maririn] Mmm-hmm.
…what if feels like to have some affection
from a relationship or a friend…
- [Maririn] Yeah.
- …so, I think it's gonna be important
- we share that with you.
- [Maririn] Totally.
At the very least, none of the guys here
would ever treat you like that, right?
- [Bo] Mmm-hmm.
- [Tai-chan] For sure.
If you don't say it out loud,
nothing will change.
- [Ruru] Yeah.
- [Ma-kun] True.
I realize now it's not gonna help
to keep it all inside.
- [Assun] Exactly.
- [Leo] Thank you.
- [Maririn] Thanks.
- [Leo] You did good.
- [Ari] That was incredible.
- Thank you.
[both giggling]
[Ruru] I love you, Maririn.
- [chuckles]
- Love you too.
[bell chiming]
[boy on PA] This part of Okinawa
is struggling with an aging population.
It's becoming a serious problem.
So, we ask you to use your youthful energy
to help the people around you.
At one time, all of you
have had the experience of not fitting in,
and now, through this experience,
you will have a chance to learn about
community and find future inspiration.
This time around,
there are a lot of participants
who have had
these rather heavy experiences.
There are quite a lot of them.
First, you had Bo, with his story
about his addiction to meth.
- Thank God he was able to kick the habit.
- I know.
I think it takes a lot of courage
- to be willing to share that too.
- [Awich] I agree.
I keep thinking of how Maririn
was so reserved at first.
- [Megumi] Yeah.
- It's 'cause of trauma.
- [Megumi] True.
- I was in a relationship
where I was the victim
of domestic violence,
- earlier in my life.
- [Megumi] Oh, I see.
People that abuse their partners
usually have a long history of it,
and that cycle of violence
is really hard to stop.
All that changes is their victims.
So once I saw the pattern,
I was able to work up the courage
to eventually break free from it.
- Mmm.
- [Nagano] Wow.
With Maririn, the fact that
she's participating in this…
[Nagano] Mmm.
…means she's trying
to take a step forward.
[Nagano] Makes sense.
It's also a good sign she's saying
that kind of thing in front of everyone.
It could mean that she's trying
to put that story behind her,
trying to look beyond her victimhood
and move toward a brighter future.
[Nagano] That's great.
[upbeat music playing]
- [Assun] Wait for me, guys!
- [Ari] The air is cleaner.
- [laughing]
- Hey, how are you!?
- [Higa] Just dandy. Come on over.
- Good?
- Hello. Take a look.
- Amazing!
[Ma-kun] It's in the middle of nowhere.
- I could use a walking stick.
- [Higa] Exactly, we're in the mountains.
- [Ruru] Feels super refreshing
- [Hikaru] Nice to meet you.
- [Assun] Nice to meet you.
- [Higa] You're all part of the group?
- [Leo] We are.
- [Bo] Yes.
[Higa] Here, take this.
- Okay.
- [Ari] A letter?
"Ms. Higa was…
an interpreter for American doctors
after the Second World War."
"For decades, she has worked diligently
to save the lives of many local people
suffering from serious illnesses."
"Ms. Higa is currently protecting
this vast nature preserve,
where the original landscape of Okinawa
shines through."
"Please use your youthful energy
to help the locals who protect
the beautiful land of Okinawa
and its plentiful natural resources."
- Okay.
- [Ma-kun] Sounds good.
- It's nice to meet you all.
- [Bo] We're all happy to be here.
MS. HIGA
Sometimes, we also take care
of local kids.
- You know, children with disabilities.
- [Assun] Okay.
Lots of those kids
don't have many friends.
So I try to help them
by keeping them company,
even if it's for an hour or two.
I try to get them
to go for nice long walks
or to do activities together.
That way, they sleep better at night.
The most important thing for me
is that this place continues
to help underprivileged children.
So, please, come back as much as you can.
Okay? So are you all from the mainland?
- Yes, we are.
- I see. Gotcha.
Right, right. Joto!
- Yes!
- Joto!
[all laughing] Joto!
In Okinawa, whenever something
good happens and the stars align,
you say, "Joto."
- Oh, yeah.
- [Ruru] Seriously?
We also say "joto" when we want
to give a compliment or say thank you.
- I'll start using it after today.
- Yeah, "Joto!"
- [Hikaru] Let's use it like crazy.
- Anyway, thanks for coming.
Thank you for having us.
- Joto!
- [all laugh]
- Yep, that's how we roll in Okinawa.
- [Nagano] That's a real word?
We use that term for anything, like,
"Oh, that outfit is joto. "
Oh! So she wasn't saying that
to make it part of the show?
- I'd be surprised if she'd ever seen it.
- [all laughing]
Okay, let's go pick
some shikuwasa, shall we?
- [Ruru] Shikuwasa, really?
- Yes.
- [Hikaru] Yay!
- There's a ton of them.
- [Ruru] No way!
- There's no way we can pick them all.
- So grab what you can…
- [Ma-kun] Great.
…bring them back here,
and then squeeze them.
So you can see the whole process,
from when they're on the tree
up until they're bottled and ready.
- Cool.
- [all] Joto!
- [laughing]
- Joto!
Okay! Yes, let's go, all right?
- Let's go. Let's do this.
- Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
- [Assun] Let's go.
- [Hikaru] They're huge!
- [Higa] Here, there's a bunch.
- I feel like we'll pick a lot.
- Oh, gosh, I hope you do.
- Isn't this great?
- I wanna try the juice.
- Start here?
[Higa] It's better for the tree
if you pick them all.
- [Tai-chan] I didn't know that.
- That true?
- [Tai-chan] Gotcha.
- [Ma-kun] Makes sense.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
Man, I love this kind of thing. So dope.
- [Maririn] How do you do it?
- Like this.
- Have you done this kind of thing before?
- [Bo] No.
- [laughs]
- [Higa] Don't be shy, get in there.
Actually, in Juvie.
- Juvie?
- [Nagano] Said it like it's nothing.
- Put me on your shoulders.
- [Leo] Hop on.
- On my shoulders?
- [Ruru] Here I go.
- [Leo] Okay.
- [Megumi] Wow.
- [Ruru] Hold on.
- [Leo] Ready?
- One, two, three, up we go.
- [Ruru] Oh, this is great.
Don't smack me with a branch.
I'll lose an eye.
- [Ruru laughing]
- And I'll be like, "Joto!" Thanks a lot.
Quit laughing and pick 'em already.
Oh, my God, you're the worst, Leo.
[Megumi] They're getting a lot closer.
- There's a tiny one here.
- Check this one.
Oh, that looks great.
[Ruru] Doesn't it feel great
that we're helping out by doing this?
[Ma-kun] For sure.
I've, um, done a lot of different kinds
of volunteer work.
It definitely feeds me.
I'm the type of person who finds
a lot of meaning in serving others.
Like, after the earthquake in 2011,
I was around 15 at the time,
so I was pretty young,
but I went to do volunteer work then too.
Now, I help out at cafeterias
for children in need.
I donate to places like that too.
I like to spend my money on things
that can help people.
- Impressive.
- Amazing. So cool.
Well done.
[Maririn] If you've been to prison,
can you legally get a passport?
[Nagano]
What the heck are they talking about?
[Bo] You might be able to get one
for the US and Central America,
but there's some kind of long process.
- [Maririn] Really?
- [Bo] I have a criminal record.
- That's right.
- I can't travel there.
If you have a criminal record,
it's a lot harder to get a passport.
Oh, okay, so that's true.
- You know everything, professor.
- [Nagano] She does! World traveler here.
- [Tai-chan] Hey, Hikaru.
- [Hikaru] Hmm?
- [Tai-chan] Let's start picking over here.
- [Hikaru] Sounds good.
- [Ari] Look, it's huge!
- [Tai-chan] You use purple shampoo?
- [Hikaru] Yeah.
- [Tai-chan] I knew it. I use it too.
- [Awich] Well, he's a hairstylist.
- [Megumi] That explains it.
[Tai-chan] You're cute.
- Did you just blush?
- [Hikaru] Hmm?
- Nah.
- You didn't blush?
- No, but that gave me a good boost.
- [Tai-chan] Really? You're cute.
- [Hikaru] Yeah. [laughs]
You're like a rebellious,
feminist white girl.
[Hikaru] I'm not a white girl!
- Your skin's pretty light.
- [Hikaru] My Korean side.
Oh, you're Korean?
- I have a Korean sense of style.
- [Hikaru] Do you?
- We like the same fashion.
- Well, I'm a quarter Korean.
- [Ari] What?
- [Hikaru] Yeah, I am.
If you saw me without makeup,
you'd be able to tell.
- Now I wanna see you without makeup.
- Okay.
- For real?
- Sure.
[Ari] That's all I can think about now.
[Hikaru] Then keep daydreaming
while you pick shikuwasa.
[Ari] Yes, ma'am.
[Hikaru] Oh! Whoops, dropped one.
It almost landed on your head.
I don't know. I was just like,
"She's always talking to Taisei."
Like… [groans]
And, if we're gonna go that route,
bring it on.
If we end up liking the same person,
we'll just go head to head.
So, yeah, if he wants to be rivals,
let's do it. That's where I'm at.
She'll see I'm a better match.
I wanna show her that her future
would be better with me in it.
Better than with Taisei.
- Gosh, it smells good.
- Yeah, get a whiff of that!
- [Assun] I think they have to wash these.
- [Higa] Good job.
- [Higa] This way.
- Yeah.
- [Higa] We make the juice here.
- Thanks!
[Higa] Yep.
- [grunts]
- [Leo] Hmm?
[Higa] Okay.
- [Ruru] Must be tough doing this.
- [Hikaru] Let me see.
- [Bo] Careful, water's hot.
- We don't normally do stuff like this.
- Great experience.
- [Bo] Towel, please.
- [Higa] That tattoo, is that a map?
- I get asked that a lot.
- [laughing] Love that. She's so curious.
- [Megumi] Oh, wow.
Yep. She's fearless.
- It looks like a map.
- [Tai-chan] It's not a map.
- It's not?
- It's lightning.
- Lightning?
- Uh, yeah.
I'm surprised you'd draw lightning
on such a pretty face.
- You think it's pretty?
- [Higa] Of course, you're handsome!
[Tai-chan] That's flattering. Thank you.
- [Higa] See that?
- [Leo] Mmm-hmm.
- [Ruru] Amazing!
- [Higa] Pretty cool, right?
- [Leo] Oh, yeah!
- [Ruru] That's seriously amazing.
[Bo] So, do they add sugar at all?
- [Assun] 'Course you'd ask that.
- [Bo laughs]
- [Ma-kun] It smells so good.
- [Higa] Okay, gather around.
- Let's eat first.
- [Ruru] Yeah, I'm hungry.
- [Tai-chan] Looks incredible.
- [Higa] Here you go.
- [Ruru] Looks so good.
- [Tai-chan] Can't wait.
- Okay, dig in.
- Thanks for all this.
- Looks incredible.
- Thank you.
- [Hikaru] I want the juice first.
- [Higa] Does everyone have a cup?
- Is it good?
- Sour!
- [Tai-chan] Yum.
- [Higa] Tart, right?
- [Megumi] I bet that stuff's good for you.
- It's tasty.
[Higa] You like it?
- [Ruru] Delicious!
- Food's amazing.
- [Higa] Good?
- Yeah.
[Higa] That's good to hear. But, listen.
No matter what happened in your past,
if you're happy right now
and you have a decent job,
isn't that really all you need in life?
Because, you know,
in this day and age, well,
things are… things are getting
a little dark and scary.
Children killing their parents,
and parents killing their children,
it's really painful
just to think about it.
When I hear about these terrible things,
it makes me wonder how…
I mean, they probably felt like they had
a good reason to do it at the time,
but I always wonder if there was anything
that could've been done
to prevent it from happening. Hmm?
So, I think it's a good idea
for all of you
to keep that in mind in the future.
Uh, I think a lot of us here,
we wanna find love.
[Higa] Mmm-hmm.
What should we do
if we find someone we're interested in?
That's easy.
Put on a nice, big smile and say hello!
- [Ruru laughs] So cute!
- That works.
- [Assun] Might be the best first step.
- I'm not kidding. That's what I'd do.
- If you find someone you like.
- Should we just say how we feel?
Don't confess right away.
- Little by little?
- [Higa] Don't scare them off.
Even if you want to tell them right away,
if you just tell her everything at once,
she might get overwhelmed with anxiety
and pull away.
- [Ari] Mmm.
- Mmm.
- That's great advice from a legend.
- A legend, huh?
- Totally. Hit the nail on the head.
- She's got all the dating tips.
That makes sense.
- [Higa] Best of luck.
- Thanks, I'll need it.
- [Ruru] She's too much.
- [Ari] Aye-aye, captain!
- We had an amazing time.
- [Higa] Really? I'm glad to hear that.
We'd never get an experience like this.
What time we meeting tomorrow?
To chop wood?
[all laugh]
- [Leo] Noon?
- Let's see. What time is good?
- 5:00 a.m. sharp?
- [all laughing]
Sorry, uh, no, no, sorry.
- I was kidding.
- [Higa] Kidding?
- I got carried away.
- [Higa] Right.
Uh, so, did anybody else
notice that old lady's hands?
- They were brown.
- [Hikaru] Yeah.
I think that comes from
going through that process every day.
Her hands tell the story
of the work she does.
- It's gotta be tough.
- [Ma-kun] Dude. For sure.
When you stop and think
she's been doing that every day
for the past 40 years,
it's seriously amazing, right?
- She's so cool.
- That kind of environment
can really be good for troubled kids.
It's perfect for them.
They get that level of care and attention.
And then, the kids who got
that kind of help in life,
they eventually grow up,
and they have the tools and opportunities
to give back to kids
in the same situation they were in.
- I just think that's really wonderful.
- Mmm.
Yeah, I really think…
we'd all be better off
if we tried to value stuff like that.
- Definitely.
- That old lady was so warm and sweet.
[bell chiming]
[Megumi] I'm glad everyone had a chance
to take in that experience.
[boy on PA]
Time for the evening sauna session.
- [Ruru] Oh?
- Oh, now?
[boy on PA] The person selected
for the sauna this time
was able to find their courage,
and open up about their past.
- Congrats, Maririn.
- [Hikaru] What?
[Ari] Maririn, yeah!
[boy on PA] You may now choose the man
you're interested in.
- [Ari] Well deserved!
- [Ruru] This is so exciting.
- [Leo] She was so brave!
- [Ari] So happy for you.
- [Ruru] You killed it.
- [Maririn] For real. Okay.
Let me see… Wait, this feels like
- a really tough decision.
- [Hikaru] This is tricky.
How about we have the guys
go somewhere else?
- [Ari] Good idea.
- For a little bit.
- The guys will go somewhere.
- We'll call you back.
- [Leo] Don't want us eavesdropping.
- [Hikaru] Exactly.
- [Ari] No problem.
- Wanna talk about it?
- [Maririn] I guess so.
- Sit here.
So, how many are there?
- [Maririn] What?
- Choices?
- Let's see…
- [Ari] Boys, hit the road.
Okay, so, like, I've been talking
to Tai-chan, but, well…
- [giggling]
- [chuckling]
But, honestly, I'm thinking Leo.
- Oh!
- Yeah, so…
'Cause, I don't know, I don't think
Tai-chan wants to keep talking to me.
I gave him a letter yesterday,
but he hasn't said anything since.
[Megumi] Interesting.
So she's sensing something is off.
[Ruru] So Tai-chan or Leo?
- I think so.
- [Ruru] For now.
To be honest,
I wanna cook with Leo after this.
- So I don't want him to go.
- [Assun] Oh!
- It's heating up in here.
- [Nagano] Shots fired.
[Ruru] You decided?
What should we do with the guys?
- Guys, we're ready.
- [Megumi] They really did stay away, huh?
- [Awich] They're running back.
- [Megumi] So cute.
[Ari] Wassup, wassup?
- God, they're all just staring her down.
- They're all looking at me.
- [laughs]
- Super intense.
[Ruru] Maririn is about to say
who she wants to go into the sauna with.
- [Ruru and Ari mimic drum roll]
- [laughs]
- Leo.
- [Ma-kun exclaims]
Okay, let's go.
- [Hikaru] Nice.
- [Ruru] So fast.
[Hikaru] You ever seen someone
jump up so fast?
- [Assun] Everyone jumps at the chance.
- [Hikaru] Eager beaver.
- [Nagano] Wow!
- Not fun for her, huh?
- [chuckling] Not much of a poker face.
- [Megumi laughs]
- She wears her heart on her sleeve.
- [Nagano] Girl can't hide her feelings.
She puts everything out in the open.
- [Maririn] Later.
- [Hikaru] Have fun.
- [Assun] How are you feeling?
- Doesn't exactly make me feel great.
- [Assun] Yeah, I bet.
- Mmm-hmm.
I even told her
I didn't want her to go with Leo.
- [Assun] I know.
- You told her? Just now?
- [Ruru] I did.
- [Assun] She did.
- [Ari] What did she say?
- [Ruru] She's going with him anyway.
- She's feisty.
- [laughs]
- Yeah. Maririn's a spicy one.
- [Ma-kun] Bro, she's built different.
The thing is, I've never talked to him.
And he's the one
I want to get to know the most.
So, I'm really curious to see
what it's like with just the two of us.
Maririn is basically…
She's only just beginning to open up.
And it seems like
she wants to get to know everyone.
And, don't get me wrong,
I want her to have a great time
and fall in love with someone here.
But if Maririn wants to go for Leo,
I'm cool with it,
but I'm gonna be like,
"We're gonna throw down, girl."
[Nagano] Oh, that's good.
- That bathrobe looks good on you.
- You like it?
[chuckles] You were made for that.
- Feel like a rich guy.
- It's giving yakuza vibes.
- Oh, come on.
- [Maririn giggling]
Oh, wow.
- [Maririn] Oh, you have tattoos.
- Yeah, I do.
- For real? That's surprising.
- [Leo] Really? You think so?
[Maririn] I didn't think you had any.
I saw the ones on your legs.
- [Leo] Let's go in.
- [Maririn] Sounds good. [chuckles]
[sultry music playing]
- [Leo] Sandals. We can go with these.
- [Maririn] Let's put them on.
- [Leo] Ready?
- [Maririn] Yeah. Oh, it's hot.
[Leo] Why did you choose me?
[Maririn] I thought the way
you listened to her was was really nice.
Yeah. Oh, I've got a bunch
of back tats too.
Wow, that's incredible.
- [Maririn] How far do these go?
- [Leo] Nice, yeah? Butt crack.
- No kidding. It's really--
- Like 'em?
[Maririn] They look amazing.
I don't know much about art, but--
- [Leo] The colors are pretty bold, right?
- [Maririn] So wild.
It caught me off guard, and I love it.
- [Leo] You didn't expect it? It's a plus.
- Yeah, not at all.
- Yeah.
- [Leo] That's good.
Everything the girls say about you
is a plus too.
- [Maririn chuckles]
- Uh… Mmm.
You seem like a really nice guy.
I loved the way you were listening earlier
to, um, Higa, that old lady?
- You were looking her in the eye.
- Mmm.
That's when I started thinking,
- "Maybe he's a good guy."
- Mmm.
[boy on PA] All of you worked hard
to help someone from the community,
so as a reward for your commitment,
you may have alcohol.
- Yay!
- [Megumi] Look how happy Assun is.
- I love it.
- [Ruru] Let's make dinner!
- [Ma-kun] Heck yeah!
- [Ruru] This is the best.
[Ma-kun] Maybe I'll become
a shikuwasa farmer.
What about my reward?
Oh, shoot, right.
I forgot, you don't drink.
- We should give her a reward.
- [Ma-kun] Right.
That's right, I forgot she's sober too.
[Ari] Hey, why the long face?
What's wrong? Come on, cheer up.
You know what?
- I'm not gonna drink tonight either.
- [Nagano exclaims]
- Really?
- Yeah.
It wouldn't feel right
if you're the only one not drinking.
- [Nagano] That's sweet.
- So, if you can't drink, I can't either.
How's that sound?
Mmm. You're scoring points.
- [Ari] Oh, I'm scoring, huh?
- Mmm-hmm.
Thanks. Nailed it.
This is the real wassup moment.
Like, "Let's hype it up."
- Whoa, it's cold.
- [Maririn] No way.
[Leo chuckles] It's crazy.
Ah! Wait. [chuckling] That's freezing.
Oh, you're dead.
- [laughing]
- [Leo] Time out, that's cold!
- [Megumi] Ah, carefree youth.
- [both laugh]
[Maririn]
Feels like we're kids at a pool party.
- Today was my first step.
- [Leo] A step forward? You took it.
- That's right.
- It was a big first step.
- It was huge for me.
- I want you to keep going.
- [Maririn] Oh, I will.
- [Leo] Mmm-hmm.
[Maririn] From now on.
I mean, I don't even remember what I said.
My mind went completely blank.
Like, seriously, it was just a reflex.
Like my spinal cord was talking
or something, or my bones.
- [laughs] You heard it here first.
- [Awich exclaims]
What does she mean by,
"My spinal cord was talking"?
That's amazing.
- Those words don't come out easily.
- [Megumi] Not from the spinal cord.
I've always liked anatomy.
- [Nagano] Is that right?
- I find it moving.
[Nagano] Really? That's creepy, no?
So, my heart was racing,
for the first time in a while, with him.
And Ruru said
she didn't feel any sauna magic,
but, obviously, I did.
There's no doubt about it.
- [Ruru] Make room, guys.
- [Ari] I'll do the dishes.
- It's fine.
- I'll do it.
- [Assun] Are we making meat loaf?
- Want a beer?
I'm good.
- I never find anything in this kitchen.
- [Ma-kun exclaims] Really?
- Not tonight. I made a promise.
- [Ma-kun] Good for you.
[Tai-chan] Here.
- Anyone helping me set the table?
- [Tai-chan] You're pretty.
- [Tai-chan] Did that make you happy?
- I don't know.
- Uh…
- Huh?
I don't know
if I want you to say it that much.
- Okay. Only on special occasions?
- [Hikaru] Yeah.
[Tai-chan] Okay.
[Ruru] What is he talking about?
- Do we even have enough towels?
- [Tai-chan] You're blushing.
[Hikaru] I tell you to say it,
and then not to.
- God, these two.
- [Hikaru] I'm like a cat.
[Tai-chan] Exactly.
You act cold, but you're sweet.
- [Ari] Anyone else helping?
- We're all a little distracted.
Yeah, they're super close, aren't they?
He's annoying as hell.
I just want to beat his ass.
Like, bro,
I could put your lights out. [laughs]
That's how I used to be.
No, that'd be super lame of me.
We're just gonna have to compete
for her love, fair and square.
I think men are more attractive
when they're calm,
so I'm gonna try to play it cool.
[Ruru] Let's eat!
- Thank you for the food!
- Hear, hear.
Nice. Mmm.
- [Ma-kun] Mmm, delicious.
- Mmm.
- [Ruru] The miso soup's great.
- Yeah, it's spicy.
- Oh, so good!
- [Ma-kun] Yeah, we nailed it.
- [Ruru] They're back.
- [Hikaru] Welcome back!
- [Tai-chan] Yo. Come.
- [Ma-kun] Welcome back.
The evening sauna is something else.
It was amazing.
- Hey, was there sauna magic?
- [Leo] Huh?
- [Hikaru] Sauna magic.
- That's one thing,
- the whole vibe is crazy.
- [Bo] Sounds incredible.
- You guys have a deep conversation?
- Mmm.
Well, it was so hot.
And my mind went blank, so I feel like
I don't remember what I said at all.
Was it the heat
or was it something you did?
Huh? Whoa! Huh? That's wild!
- [laughing] Oh, God.
- [Hikaru laughing]
- [Maririn] I wouldn't say…
- [Leo] No.
- [all laughing]
- Don't go making up your own story.
- Something's fishy.
- Especially with these two idiots.
- [Leo] Good night.
- [women] Night.
- [Bo] Night.
- [Hikaru] Good night.
So, how was it?
Well, it didn't get romantic or anything.
Mmm.
After talking to him for a while,
I realized I'm still
kind of scared of love.
You are, right? Gotta say, that tracks.
- [Maririn] Yeah.
- For sure.
Wait, Tai-chan was coming on to you
pretty strong.
Didn't he ask
if he could invite you to the sauna?
- [Ruru] Oh, really?
- Those two were really intense today.
- [Assun] Who?
- Ari and Tai-chan.
- [Maririn] They were all over you.
- Tell us.
It's like my letter never happened, right?
- Was it a dream?
- Does feel like that.
- [Assun] Odd.
- Did I dream that?
It's super weird.
[Maririn] Yesterday, I gave him a letter
while you were talking, right?
I heard about that. Gotcha.
- I heard about that.
- What'd he say?
Like, he basically said
he's not really interested
in talking to you one-on-one again,
or writing you a letter back anytime soon.
- What?
- [Ruru] Huh?
- That's not an answer, is it?
- [Hikaru] I don't know.
I didn't hear what the letter said.
If that's true, Tai-chan's messed up.
I pretty much wrote I was into him.
I said I wanted him to talk to me more
and come on stronger,
that I was interested in him.
So should I take the hint?
- [Ruru] What's that mean?
- It's confusing.
- That guy's not a man. He's immature.
- [Maririn] I told him he's not a real man.
- [Assun] If it's a no, he should say so.
- Mmm, mmm, yeah.
What he said to me was,
"I've already decided on you, Hikaru."
- That's what he should tell me.
- [Hikaru] Yeah, so that's…
It shows respect to you, too,
if he'd just tell me that. Be a man.
What's stopping him
from just telling Maririn
that he's already decided on Hikaru?
- Oh, yeah, I gotcha.
- [Maririn] Seriously.
Hikaru lets it all out, too, huh?
No filter.
- She really does.
- Yeah, she doesn't hold back.
They're talking about a guy
who likes her right now, though.
I mean, I feel like for all of us,
that's not what we want.
That's not what we're looking for.
'Cause up until now,
we've been in relationships with men
who have some integrity.
And we came to Badly In Love
looking for more of that kind of guy.
- [Assun] We're not looking for trash.
- [Ruru] Yeah.
I just wanna give Tai-chan
a piece of my mind.
[Assun] Let's teach him a lesson.
"Hey, you dick!"
Maririn, you should talk to him now
while your feelings are fresh.
- [Maririn] Right.
- [Assun] And if he starts dodging,
we'll step in.
We should all
just roll up on him ourselves.
Yeah, 'cause, I mean,
Maririn has a huge amount of trauma
when it comes to relationships.
So the least Tai-chan could do
is give her an answer.
He's being such a child right now.
- So lame.
- [Assun] Totally.
- [inhales sharply]
- This is scary, right?
- When the ladies start to get like this.
- Terrifying.
Okay, that sounds good.
[tense music playing]
[sniffles]
[music stops]
- Yoo-hoo.
- Hey, hey.
- Yoo-hoo. What's up?
- What's up?
Tai-chan, let's chat.
- [Tai-chan] Now?
- Yeah.
- [Nagano groans]
- Let's go.
- [Megumi] Tai-chan has no clue.
- [Nagano] Well, he's red.
- [Maririn] I'm borrowing him.
- No problem.
- Sure, use him as much as you want.
- [Maririn chuckles]
You got five hours.
- [Maririn] Let's go to the classroom?
- [Tai-chan] The classroom?
- [Maririn] Yeah, I want to talk to you.
- [Tai-chan] Sure.
This is brutal!
- Those guys were drinking so much too.
- Oh, man.
He's probably thinking,
"Maybe she's gonna say she likes me."
Yeah, probably.
Okay, so, I gave you a letter, right?
It feels like you're pretending
that never happened.
[Tai-chan] Mmm.
- 'Cause, like, you never directly…
- Yeah. I never said anything.
So, what's going on? Or, like,
I don't know, why didn't you say anything?
We could've talked
during the shikuwasa-picking.
- Well, yeah, I guess that's true. Hmm.
- Uh-huh.
I feel like you're trying to avoid
talking to me right now too.
So, was I just not even on your radar?
That's not it,
but the thing is, I don't know,
- I also, you know…
- [Maririn] Yeah.
This stuff with Hikaru…
- I have feelings for her.
- [Maririn] Mmm.
[Tai-chan] And then, suddenly, you know,
I got that letter from you, Maririn.
Um…
- And, you know, so, the thing is, I, uh…
- Hmm?
- [laughs] Oh, yikes!
- It's safe to say he's rattled.
[laughs] Hold on, maybe he's a good kid.
When it comes to love,
it's a one-way street for me.
- Mmm. And?
- Mmm.
If I feel like she's the one for me,
I think I should go straight for her now.
- Yeah, that's what a man would do.
- Mmm.
But, look, if you like her
and still want to get to know other girls,
- I think that's fine too.
- There's no other girls. Not for me.
[Maririn] Okay, so who's your pick?
At this point, I'm kind of
on a one-way street toward Hikaru.
- [Maririn] "Kind of"?
- I'm on a one-way street. Mmm.
So are you just pretending
my letter never existed at all?
- I don't want you to think that.
- Then what's going on?
Hmm…
I guess I was waiting for you
to make a move.
- Waiting for me?
- [Tai-chan] Um…
- I told you how I felt in the letter.
- [Tai-chan] Mmm.
But you…
wanted more?
Hmm…
Pretty much.
What?
You can't say something like that
to her face.
All right.
[Maririn] Mmm…
But, yeah, I wanna be honest
with you here. Mmm.
I'm sorry.
- Really…
- Can you wait here for a bit?
- Sure.
- [Nagano] What?
- [Megumi] Huh?
- [Awich] Is this what I think it is?
- You cold?
- No, I want you to wait here.
- [Nagano] Scary.
- [Megumi] Yeah.
- [Maririn] It's messed up.
- What?
[Maririn]
He's dodging the whole conversation.
- Let's roll.
- Oh, snap!
- Ah! Here they come.
- No, no, no, no.
- Come on, girl, just take the hint.
- They're gonna jump him!
[Maririn] He did say he's on
a "one-way street toward Hikaru,"
so I asked him if that meant
he's pretending he never got my letter.
And he said, "Mmm, it's not like that,
but I guess I was waiting for you
to make a move."
- What?
- [Maririn] He's like,
"I was waiting for you
to come talk to me."
- But you'd already written him a letter.
- [Maririn] I was like, "What?"
- [Assun] You're not on the same page.
- He was dodging, then said sorry.
- I'm thinking, "We're done."
- [Megumi] Man, they're all so feisty.
- What? Hikaru's the one who should go.
- I know. Think about it.
Hikaru was adding plenty of fuel
to the fire.
[door opens]
- [Ruru] You asleep? [laughs]
- [Assun] Wake up.
- [Ruru] Rise and shine.
- [Assun] You're half asleep.
Stay awake.
I came here because I was pissed off
after I heard what you said.
[Tai-chan] Mmm.
There is so much
I want to say to you, Tai-chan.
Here's the thing
we've all been looking for…
A real man in our relationships.
You know, not a boy.
We all came to this school
looking for that.
- [Tai-chan] Mmm.
- So if this is the kind of guy you are,
- none of us need you, okay?
- Mmm.
[Ruru] It's like you're not taking
Maririn's trauma seriously.
That's not right.
I honestly think you're a piece of trash.
[Ruru] Mmm-hmm.
[Assun] If you don't change,
if you can't act like a man,
then no one
is going to love you, Tai-chan.
- Wow. [laughing]
- Did she need to go that far? [laughs]
- Can you call someone trash on TV?
- Incredible.
He looked like he got his finger
caught in a honey trap, didn't he?
- [laughing]
- [Nagano] Poor Tai-chan.
Who knows what'll happen to him?
- Now that's a cliffhanger.
- What'll happen to Tai-chan?
[laughs] He is pretty much
hanging off the cliff.
[all laughing]
[closing theme song playing]